Guide to the Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 587 Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 587 records, 1941-2012; 1980-2010; 5680-001; 15 cubic feet 17 boxes
  - ATU 587 MATERIALS, 1941-2011; SERIES I
    - ATU 587 Publications and Materials for ATU 587 Members, 1941-2011; Subseries A
      - Part 3: Collective Bargaining Agreements (Contracts), 1973-2010
        - Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) between ATU 587 and King County Metro Transit, exp. 2001 (Box-folder 1/14)
        - Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) between ATU 587 and King County Metro Transit, exp. 2004 (Box-folder 1/15)
        - Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) between ATU 587 and King County Metro Transit, exp. 2007 (Box-folder 1/16)
        - Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) between ATU 587 and King County Metro Transit, exp. 2010 (Box-folder 1/17)
        - Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) between ATU 587 and King County Metro Transit, Addendum for Rail Employees, 2010 (Box-folder 2/1)
        - Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) between ATU 587 and Paratransit (MV) Public Transportation, 2004-2007 (Box-folder 2/2)
        - Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) between ATU 587 and Paratransit (MV) Transportation, 2007 (Box-folder 2/3)
        - Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) between ATU 587 and Seattle Personal Transit, 2002-2005 (Box-folder 2/4)
        - Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) between ATU 587 and Seattle Personal Transit, 2005-2008 (Box-folder 2/5)
        - Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) between ATU 587 and Seattle Personal Transit, 2008-2009 (Box-folder 2/6)
        - Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) between ATU 587 and Seattle Personal Transit, 2009-2012 (Box-folder 2/7)
        - Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) between ATU 587 and Paratransit Services, 2004-2006 (Box-folder 2/8)
        - Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) between ATU 587 and Paratransit Services, 2007-2009 (Box-folder 2/9)
        - Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) between ATU 587 and Paratransit Services, 2010-2012 (Box-folder 2/10)
        - Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) between ATU 587 and First Transit Call Center, 2010-2014 (Box-folder 2/11)
        - Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) between ATU 587 and Jefferson Transit Authority, 1984 (Box-folder 2/12)
        - Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) between ATU 587 and Jefferson Transit Authority, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 2/13)
        - Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) between ATU 587 and Jefferson Transit Authority, 2005-2007 (Box-folder 2/14)
        - Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) between ATU 587 and Jefferson Transit Authority, 2008-2010 (Box-folder 2/15)
        - Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) between ATU 587 and Clallam Transit System Authority, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 2/16)
        - Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) between ATU 587 and Clallam Transit System Authority, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 2/17)
        - Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) between ATU 587 and Clallam Transit System, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 2/18)
        - Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) between ATU 587 and Clallam Transit System, 2001-2003 (Box-folder 2/19)
        - Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) between ATU 587 and Clallam Transit System, 2004-2006 (Box-folder 2/20)
        - Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) between ATU 587 and Clallam Transit System, 2010-2014 (Box-folder 2/21)
      - Part 4: Newsletters, 1981-2011
        Subseries B consists of the ATU 587 News Letter, changed to News Review, a newsletter produced by the union that ranges from 1981 to 2011.
        - ATU 587 News Letter Feb, July 1981, Feb. 1981 (Box-folder 2/36)
        - ATU 587 News Review Oct.-Nov. 1983, Oct. 1983 (Box-folder 2/37)
        - ATU 587 News Review Jan.-June 1984, Jan. 1984 (Box-folder 2/38)
        - ATU 587 News Review July-Oct., Dec. 1984, July 1984; Oct. 1984 (Box-folder 2/39)
        - ATU 587 News Review Jan., Mar.-June 1985, Jan. 1985; Mar. 1985-June 1985 (Box-folder 2/40)
        - ATU 587 News Review July-Dec. 1985, July 1985-Dec. 1985 (Box-folder 3/1)
        - ATU 587 News Review Jan.-June 1986, Jan. 1986-June 1986 (Box-folder 3/2)
        - ATU 587 News Review July-Dec. 1986 (Box-folder 3/3)
        - ATU 587 News Review Jan.-June 1987 (Box-folder 3/4)
        - ATU 587 News Review July-Oct. 1987 (Box-folder 3/5)
        - ATU 587 News Review Jan.-June 1988 (Box-folder 3/6)
        - ATU 587 News Review July-Dec. 1988 (Box-folder 3/7)
        - ATU 587 News Review Jan.-June 1989 (Box-folder 3/8)
        - ATU 587 News Review July-Dec. 1989 (Box-folder 3/9)
        - ATU 587 News Review Jan.-June 1990 (Box-folder 3/10)
        - ATU 587 News Review Aug.-Sept., Dec. 1990, Aug. 1990-Sept. 1990 (Box-folder 3/11)
        - ATU 587 News Review Jan., May 1991, Jan. 1991 (Box-folder 3/12)
        - ATU 587 News Review July-Dec. 1991 (Box-folder 3/13)
        - ATU 587 News Review Jan.-June 1992 (Box-folder 3/14)
        - ATU 587 News Review July-Nov. 1992 (Box-folder 3/15)
        - ATU 587 News Review Jan.-June 1993 (Box-folder 3/16)
        - ATU 587 News Review July-Sept., Nov.-Dec. 1993, July-Sept. 1993 (Box-folder 3/17)
        - ATU 587 News Review Jan.-June 1994 (Box-folder 3/18)
        - ATU 587 News Review July-Dec. 1994 (Box-folder 3/19)
        - ATU 587 News Review Jan.-June 1995 (Box-folder 3/20)
        - ATU 587 News Review July-Dec. 1995 (Box-folder 3/21)
        - ATU 587 News Review Jan.-June 1996 (Box-folder 3/22)
        - ATU 587 News Review July-Dec. 1996 (Box-folder 3/23)
        - ATU 587 News Review Jan.-June 1997 (Box-folder 3/24)
        - ATU 587 News Review July-Dec. 1997 (Box-folder 3/25)
        - ATU 587 News Review Jan.-June 1998 (Box-folder 3/26)
        - ATU 587 News Review July-Dec. 1998 (Box-folder 3/27)
        - ATU 587 News Review Jan.-June 1999 (Box-folder 3/28)
        - ATU 587 News Review July-Dec. 1999 (Box-folder 3/29)
        - ATU 587 News Review Jan.-June 2000 (Box-folder 3/30)
        - ATU 587 News Review July-Dec. 2000 (Box-folder 4/1)
        - ATU 587 News Review Jan.-June 2001 (Box-folder 4/2)
        - ATU 587 News Review July-Dec. 2001 (Box-folder 4/3)
        - ATU 587 News Review Jan.-June 2002 (Box-folder 4/4)
        - ATU 587 News Review July-Dec. 2002 (Box-folder 4/5)
        - ATU 587 News Review Jan.-June 2003 (Box-folder 4/6)
        - ATU 587 News Review July-Dec. 2003 (Box-folder 4/7)
        - ATU 587 News Review Jan.-June 2004 (Box-folder 4/8)
        - ATU 587 News Review July-Dec. 2004 (Box-folder 4/9)
        - ATU 587 News Review Jan.-June 2005 (Box-folder 4/10)
        - ATU 587 News Review July-Dec. 2005 (Box-folder 4/11)
        - ATU 587 News Review Jan.-June 2006 (Box-folder 4/12)
        - ATU 587 News Review July-Nov. 2006 (Box-folder 4/13)
        - ATU 587 News Review Jan.-June 2007 (Box-folder 4/14)
        - ATU 587 News Review July-Dec. 2007 (Box-folder 4/15)
        - ATU 587 News Review Jan.-June 2008 (Box-folder 4/16)
        - ATU 587 News Review July-Dec. 2008 (Box-folder 4/17)
        - ATU 587 News Review Jan.-June 2009 (Box-folder 4/18)
        - ATU 587 News Review July-Sept., Nov.-Dec. 2009, July-Sept. 2009 (Box-folder 5/1)
        - ATU 587 News Review Jan.-June 2010 (Box-folder 5/2)
        - ATU 587 News Review July-Dec. 2010 (Box-folder 5/3)
        - ATU 587 News Review Jan.-June 2011 (Box-folder 5/4)
        - ATU 587 News Review July-Dec. 2011 (Box-folder 5/5)
    - Board and Committee Minutes, 1940-1975; Subseries B
      Subseries B consists of ATU 587 minutes from late 1940 to 1975.
      Most of these minutes are arranged chronologically rather than by committee, as they were originally all kept in the same notebook, so minutes from one committee's meeting exist on the same page as minutes from another meeting. Two exceptions are Board Meeting Minutes from July 9, 1975, which were originally loose, and a set of Motor Coach Employees Security Plan Trustees Meeting Minutes, which were kept separate and range from 1958 to 1973.
      - ATU 587 Minutes, Dec. 30, 1940-Dec. 19, 1963 (Box-folder 5/6-6/1)
      - ATU 587 Board Meeting Minutes July 9, 1975 (Box-folder 6/2)
      - Motor Coach Employees Security Plan Trustees Meeting Minutes, May 28, 1958-May 14, 1973 (Box-folder 6/3)
    - Officer Elections Materials, 1997-2010; Subseries C
      Subseries C consists of materials specific to ATU 587 officer elections that ranges from 1997-2003.
      Records are in chronological order.
      - ATU 587 Voters Pamphlet, 1997 (Box-folder 6/4)
      - ATU 587 Officer Elections, 2003 (Box-folder 6/5)
      - ATU 587 Officer Elections, 2006 (Box-folder 6/6)
      - ATU 587 Officer Elections, 2009 (Box-folder 6/7)
      - ATU 587 Elections Fliers and Brochures, circa 2010 (Box-folder 6/8)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1973-1980; Subseries D (Box-folder 6/9-7/6)
      Subseries D consists of newspaper clippings related to transportation in the Puget Sound and were originally contained in a scrapbook. Clippings range from 1973 to 1980. While the material is not entirely created by the ATU 587, the arrangement and selection shows creative thought process.
      Records are arranged chronologically.
    - Ephemera and Artifacts, Undated, Circa 1998-2002; Subseries E
      Subseries E consists of ATU 587 ephemera and artifacts including pamphlets, fliers, postcards, buttons, patches, plaques, and other similar materials. Most are undated, but probably range from the 1980s to 2000s.
      - ATU 587 Postcard to Politician, Budget Cuts, Undated (Box-folder 7/8)
      - Flyers on King County Council, Undated (Box-folder 7/9)
      - Black Paratransit Services Armbands, Undated (Box-folder 7/10)
      - ATU 587 Shoulder Patch, Undated (Box-folder 7/11)
      - ATU 587 Datebook Cover, Undated (Box-folder 7/12)
      - ATU Romanian Council Plaques, circa 2002 (Box-folder 7/13)
      - Pins and Buttons, General and Committees, Undated (Box-folder 7/14)
      - Pins and Buttons, Elections, Undated (Box-folder 7/15)
      - Mark McLaughlin Memorial Cards, circa 1998 (Box-folder 7/16)
      - ATU for Obama/Biden Yard Sign, 2008 (Box-folder 17)
    - Videocassettes, 1984-2005; Subseries F
      Many of the 29 videocassettes in this Subseries F were intended for ATU 587 viewers, though they originate from many different sources, including the ATU International, local news organizations, and employer organizations.
      Items are arranged alphabetically by title.
      - ATU 1995 Convention Opening Video (Box-folder 8/1)
      - ATU Advancement Through Unity - 1986 (Box-folder 8/2)
      - ATU CDL Study Program Orientation Tape, Undated (Box-folder 8/3)
      - ATU Jerry Fund, Undated (Box-folder 8/4)
      - ATU Tapes - 1986 Seattle, WA (Box-folder 8/5)
      - ATU Trip to Olympia, Undated (Box-folder 8/6)
      - ATU "The Workers' Voice", Sept. 17, 1993 (Box-folder 8/7)
      - Aqui Se Puede, Farmworkers in Washington State, 1991 (Box-folder 8/8)
      - Best of Tunnel Closure Video, 2005 (Box-folder 8/9)
      - Financial Systems Products Corp, Undated (Box-folder 8/10)
      - Grievance Handling, Undated (Box-folder 8/11)
      - Mayworks Festival, Undated (Box-folder 8/12)
      - Mayworks Festival/Portraits of Union Women, Undated (Box-folder 8/13)
      - King 5 - Metro Security, Undated (Box-folder 8/14)
      - King 5 - "Metro Safety", Nov. 10, 1987-Nov 12, 1987; Dec. 1, 1987-Dec. 4, 1987 (Box-folder 8/15)
      - KOMO's Bullshit on Bus Drivers and King 5 Cheap Shot 5-20-94, May 20, 1994 (Box-folder 8/16)
      - Peninsula College Commercial, "Bus Drivin' Shuffle," "Clallam County - Stickin' to the Union", June 1987 (Box-folder 8/17)
      - Portraits of Union Women, 1992 (Box-folder 8/18)
      - The Role of the Shop Steward, Undated (Box-folder 8/19)
      - "A Safe Ride For All," The UMTA Rule, Undated (Box-folder 8/20)
      - Security Task Force Training Film, Undated (Box-folder 8/21)
      - Sexual Harassment in the Workplace, Undated (Box-folder 8/22)
      - Struggle in the Heartland, Undated (Box-folder 8/23)
      - Washington Citizen Action Medicare/Medicaid Presentation, Undated (Box-folder 8/24)
      - Washington Forest Protection Association, Undated (Box-folder 8/25)
      - Winning -- With ATU Committee on Political Education (COPE), Undated (Box-folder 8/26)
      - Workplace Hustle/Would You Let Someone Do This to Your Sister?, 1984 (Box-folder 8/27)
      - United Farm Workers of America Wrath of Grapes, Undated (Box-folder 8/28)
      - Untitled VHS, Undated (Box-folder 8/29)
    - Compact Discs, circa 2000s; Subseries G
      This Subseries G consists of 81 compact discs. These discs range from 2003 to 2012. Most contain photos. Of particular note are CDs from the Memorabilia folder from the ATU 587 office server.
      Discs are in their original order, as they were stored at the ATU 587.
      - Disc #2: Meetings, Memoranda on Agreement (MOA), News Review Articles, 1990s-2000s (Box-folder 16/1)
        These discs were burned for the archival donation by members of the ATU 587 office staff. The files on them contain copies of useful documents.
      - Disc #3: Section 13(c), ATU 587 Motions Log, 1990s-2000s (Box-folder 16/2)
      - Disc #8: Contracts, 1990s-2000s (Box-folder 16/3)
      - Disc #9: Bulletins; By-Laws, Rules, & Regulations, 1990s-2000s (Box-folder 16/4)
      - Memorabilia Folder Pictures, 2012; These discs include a wide variety of photos on many different topics, accumulated over the years, from the ATU office server's "Memorabilia Folder." Most were not taken in 2012, but that is the year in which the CDs were created. The folder was so large that it was burned onto 10 discs. First disc's case includes a subfolder list printout. (Box-folder 16/5-14)
      - Photos Black Caucus Sea 2005 Marc Auerbach (Box-folder 16/15)
      - 4 together, labeled "CTS": Clallam Transit System April 03 cutr May 03 Declination Glens Social Hour, 2003 (Box-folder 16/16)
      - Clallam Transit System Awards 04, 2004 (Box-folder 16/17)
      - Clallam Transit System photos as of 1-19-06, Jan. 19, 2006 (Box-folder 16/18)
      - Clallam Transit System, Undated (Box-folder 16/19)
      - John Senear '05, 2005 (Box-folder 16/20)
      - Monorail Demonstration 2-11-04, Feb. 11, 2004 (Box-folder 16/21)
      - "2004 International Convention"54th Convention September 13-17, 2004 DVD featuring Driven to Serve, Happy Faces, Safety & Security, Education, Community Service, Organizing, Sen. Clinton, Convention Highlights, Legislative & Political Action (Box-folder 16/22-25)
      - 54th Convention September 13-17, 2004 Driven to Serve Convention Anthem TRT 8:27 (Box-folder 16/26)
      - 2004 ATU International Convention Las Vegas (Box-folder 16/27)
      - King County 2004 Operators of the Month Photos (Box-folder 16/28)
      - Committee on Political Education (COPE) Form, Undated (Box-folder 16/29-39)
      - 7/22/11 entered on excel 6/9/08 Lance Norton PDR King Co. Dept of Transportation, circa 2008-2011 (Box-folder 16/40)
      - Steven Frank PDR King County DOT 1 of 1, Undated (Box-folder 16/41)
      - Portland Max, Undated (Box-folder 16/42)
      - American Federation of Government Employees (AFGE) Demo 2-26-03, 2003 (Box-folder 16/43)
      - ATU Latino Caucus-Committee on Political Education (ATULC-COPE) Jan 2004 (Box-folder 16/44)
      - Local 587 Carey Larsen Group Shot, Undated (Box-folder 16/45)
      - Lobby Day 2008 with note: Paul, here are the pix from the lobby day Thanx, Alan" (Box-folder 16/46)
      - Washington State Labor Council Convention Digital Photo Album, Undated (Box-folder 16/47)
      - "Employee Photos 2002-2008": The Kim and Cathy Tour of Greater Seattle Washington June 2002 Photos by Cathy Donalds (Box-folder 16/48)
      - Open House MDRS Mar. 2004 (Box-folder 16/49)
      - SB Safety Breakfast Mar. 2004 (Box-folder 16/50)
      - Teri Allen VM Emp of the Year the Man 2004 (Box-folder 16/51)
      - PTTO Qualification Day March 26, 2004 by Jim Elder for Paul Griffin, with note "a little something for the news review?" (Box-folder 16/52)
      - P/T class of 3-26-04 CD #2, 2004 (Box-folder 16/53)
      - Festive Annual Member Event 2005 Picnic Photos by Marie Larsen (Box-folder 16/54)
      - Office Scenes July 2005 (Box-folder 16/55)
      - Street Car 11-18-05, 2005 (Box-folder 16/56)
      - Bar-b-que, Undated (Box-folder 16/57)
      - Local 587 Picnic 2005 (Box-folder 16/58-59)
      - ATU 587 BBQ 2006 jpegs (Box-folder 16/60)
      - East Base Christmas Party 12-17-2007 (Box-folder 16/61)
      - SLU Employee Appreciation Day 2008 (Box-folder 16/62)
      - Set of photos labeled "Retirees." Retiree 05 F.A.M.E. 2960002 to 2960022, 2005 (Box-folder 16/63)
      - Retiree 05 F.A.M.E. 2950003 to 2950022, 2005 (Box-folder 16/64)
      - Solidarity and Romania for News review, Undated (Box-folder 16/65)
      - Russians pictures and story July 04, 2004 (Box-folder 16/66)
      - ATU 587 Photos Mark McLaughlin memorial 11-23-2007 (Box-folder 16/67)
      - "Northwest Conference 2004-2006": Northwest Conference 04 (Box-folder 16/68-70)
      - Northwest Conference Portland 2005 (Box-folder 16/71)
      - Northwest Conference 2005 "pick of the litter" with note "Review and send to the intl (???)" (Box-folder 16/72)
      - Northwest Conference Edmonton - 06, 2006 (Box-folder 16/73)
      - Northwest Conference best Phoenix 06, 2006 (Box-folder 16/74)
      - "How do we get there from here", Undated (Box-folder 16/75)
      - ADR - Mediation Training May 2008 Arbitration Training (Box-folder 16/76)
      - Labor Arbitration Institute 5th Ed., Undated (Box-folder 16/77)
      - Puget Sound Milestones Central Puget Sound Regional Economic Profile, 2003 (Box-folder 16/78)
      - Metro 30th Anniversary Feb 1, 2003, with note "Got some good shots, Lance. Hope you like them. Al" (Box-folder 16/79)
      - Lobby Day Committee on Political Education 03, 2003 (Box-folder 16/80)
      - Shop Steward Training Feb 06, 2006 (Box-folder 16/81)
      - Gay Pride Seattle, WA 2006 (Box-folder 16/82)
      - Election 2003 Best Pictures at random (Box-folder 16/83)
      - Trainings-metro. Calling out the stops. Peggy A. Renfrow, Chief of Bellevue Base Operations, Undated (Box-folder 16/84)
      - Health Matters Video from the King County Leadership Forum, Undated (Box-folder 16/85)
  - ATU INTERNATIONAL PUBLICATIONS, 1980s-2000s; SERIES II
    ATU International Publications is made up of material created by the ATU International.
    - Regulations, Constitutions and General Laws, 1975-2007; Subseries A
      This subseries includes publications from the ATU International related to the conduct and goals of members, local unions, and the organization as a whole. The first section contains Constitutions and General Laws from between 1977 and 2003. The second section contains other materials related to conduct, such as the ATU Ritual and Form of Initiation from 1995 and the booklet The ATU: A Brief History from 1985.
      - ATU International, Constitution and General Laws, 1977 (Box-folder 9/1)
      - ATU International, Constitution and General Laws, 1981 (Box-folder 9/2)
      - ATU International, Constitution and General Laws, 1983 (Box-folder 9/3)
      - ATU International, Constitution and General Laws, 1986 (Box-folder 9/4)
      - ATU International, Constitution and General Laws, 1989 (Box-folder 9/5)
      - ATU International, Constitution and General Laws, 1992 (Box-folder 9/6)
      - ATU International, Constitution and General Laws, 1995 (Box-folder 9/7)
      - ATU International, Constitution and General Laws, 1998 (Box-folder 9/8)
      - ATU International, Constitution and General Laws, 2001 (Box-folder 9/9)
      - ATU International, Constitution and General Laws, 2004 (Box-folder 9/10)
      - ATU International, Constitution and General Laws, 2007 (Box-folder 9/11)
      - ATU Ritual and Form of Initiation, 1995 (Box-folder 9/12)
      - ATU Women's International Auxiliary Constitution and General Laws, 1975 (Box-folder 9/13)
      - The ATU: A Brief History, 1985 (Box-folder 9/14)
      - ATU Pamphlet, Undated (Box-folder 9/15)
    - Local Union Directories, 2007-2008; Subseries B
      Subseries B includes booklets from 2007 and 2008 with the contact information for all ATU local unions.
      - ATU Local Union Directory, 2007 (Box-folder 9/16)
      - ATU Local Union Directory, 2008 (Box-folder 9/17)
    - Convention, Seminar, and Meeting Materials, 1961-2001; Subseries C
      Subseries C contains material from the Amalgamated Transit Union biennial conventions, including convention programs, proceedings, international reports, and Committee on Political Education (COPE) Reports. Documents range from 1961 to 1995 and are arranged chronologically.
      - ATU Souvenir Programed 36th Convention, 1961 (Box-folder 9/18)
      - ATU 45th Convention Proceedings, 1979 (Box-folder 9/19)
      - ATU 46th Convention Proceedings, 1981 (Box-folder 9/20)
      - ATU 46th Convention International Reports, 1981 (Box-folder 9/21)
      - ATU 47th Convention Proceedings, 1983 (Box-folder 9/22)
      - ATU 47th Convention International Reports, 1983 (Box-folder 9/23)
      - ATU 48th Convention Proceedings, 1986 (Box-folder 9/24)
      - ATU 48th Convention Program of Events, 1986 (Box-folder 9/25)
      - ATU 48th Convention Program of Events, 1986 (Box-folder 9/26)
      - ATU 48th Convention Program, 1986 (Box-folder 9/27)
      - ATU 48th Convention, ATU-Committee on Political Education (COPE), 1983-86, 1986 (Box-folder 9/28)
      - ATU Jerry Fund 1st Annual Golf Tournament, 1986 (Box-folder 9/29)
      - ATU 49th Convention Program, 1989 (Box-folder 9/30)
      - ATU 49th Convention International Reports, 1989 (Box-folder 9/31)
      - ATU 49th Convention ATU-Committee on Political Education (COPE) Report, 1986-89, 1989 (Box-folder 9/32)
      - ATU 50th Convention Program, 1992 (Box-folder 9/33)
      - ATU 50th Convention Proceedings, 1992 (Box-folder 9/34)
      - ATU 50th Convention International Reports, 1992 (Box-folder 9/35)
      - ATU 50th Convention Resolutions, 1992 (Box-folder 9/36)
      - ATU 50th Convention ATU-Committee on Political Education (COPE) Report, 1992 (Box-folder 9/37)
      - ATU 51st Convention International Reports, 1995 (Box-folder 9/38)
      - ATU 51st Convention Resolutions, 1995 (Box-folder 9/39)
      - ATU 51st Convention ATU-Committee on Political Education (COPE) Reports, 1995 (Box-folder 9/40)
      - ATU 53rd Convention Proceedings, 2001 (Box-folder 9/41)
      - ATU Collective Bargaining Seminar, 1993 (Box-folder 9/42)
      - ATU Collective Bargaining Seminar, 1994 (Box-folder 9/43)
      - ATU Collective Bargaining Seminar, 1995 (Box-folder 10/1)
    - ATU International Ephemera, circa 1980s-2000s; Undated; Subseries D
      Subseries D contains one piece of ephemera, a clip-on watch from the ATU Committee on Political Education (COPE).
      - ATU-Committee on Political Education (COPE) Watch, circa 1980s-2000s; Undated (Box-folder 10/2)
    - ATU International Newsletter, May 2004-Feb. 2006; Subseries E (Box-folder 17)
      Subseries E contains copies of the ATU International Newsletter In Transit from May 2004 to Feb. 2006, arranged chronologically.
      - ATU International Journal "In Transit", May 2004-Oct. 2004 (Box-folder 17)
      - ATU International Journal "In Transit", Jan. 2005-Aug. 2005 (Box-folder 17)
      - ATU International Journal "In Transit", Sept. 2005-Feb. 2006 (Box-folder 17)
  - CITY OF SEATTLE, METRO TRANSIT, AND KING COUNTY METRO MATERIALS, 1930s-2009; SERIES III
    This series is subdivided by publication type, and within each section items are organized chronologically.